{
    "id": "ea756b7f87c64912a2840409bb165720",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There is no ............................... in talking to him.",
            "description": "The correct expression is no point in.",
            "answers": [
                "point",
                "worth",
                "use"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The rain played havoc ............................... our plans.",
            "description": "The correction expression is play havoc with.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. all I know, she is still in love with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "For",
                "As",
                "With"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I look forward .................................... you.",
            "description": "The correct expression is look forward to + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to meet",
                "for meeting",
                "to meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I told you ................................... me.",
            "description": "We make the negative form of the infinitive by putting not before to.",
            "answers": [
                "to not touch",
                "not to touch",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. the time we reach there, the train will have left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "By",
                "In",
                "After"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Time .................................. all wounds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heals",
                "cures",
                "remedies"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't believe how .................................. I am.",
            "description": "When you are out of shape, you are in a very bad condition.",
            "answers": [
                "out of order",
                "out of shape",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I had to wash the clothes by hand because the washing machine was ....................................",
            "description": "If a machine is out of order, it is not working.",
            "answers": [
                "out of shape",
                "out of order",
                "out of condition"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They burst ................................. tears after losing the championship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "out into",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We reached on time .................................... the rain.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition. It is used before a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "in spite of",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. having a cold, I managed to enjoy the party.",
            "description": "We use despite before a noun or an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}